# Jalal

#### 132-0121-6989 | jalaliden@foxmail.com



#### **SUMMARY**

I am majored in software engineering, Hunan University. My most used developing language is Python, I have backend development experience with Django and FastAPI frameworks. I am familiar with Mysql and Ubuntu, can complete an ordinary project development independently. I have a good spoken English ability, strong logical thinking. My personality is optimistic and cheerful, I also have good communication skills and team spirit.

### **EDUCATION**

Hunan University. Sep 2018 - Jul 2022

Software engineering. Bachelor College of Computer Science and Electronic Engineering.

Major courses: C ++ Program Designing, Data Structure, Algorithms, Operating System, Database Designing, Computer Network, Software Engineering, Compiling Principle, Digital Circuits, Software Testing, etc.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

北京道远教育科技有限公司 Jul 2021 - Present

Backend developer intern Technology Department

Beijing

As a backend developer intern, I will do some requirements myself, sometimes with the leading by my mentor. Mostly, I will be responsible for developing some interfaces, functions, database designing, etc. We use FastAPI(Python) framework, also use MySQL, Redis, MongoDB, Docker and other else.

## PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Email system Mar 2021 - Jun 2021

backend developer

Project Address: https://github.com/watremons/djangomail

This project includes administrator webpage (Vue + Django), ordinary user mini program(Wechat), and server back end (Django, SMTP, POP3). I mainly took responsible for the development of backend, database designing.

## Voice recognition research project

Feb 2021 - Jul 2021

Voice recognition system core developer

In this project I have trained our own speech module via using GMM&HMM and deep learning algorithms, and made an online speech recognition System, which uses Viterbi Algorithm for decoding. I mainly took responsible for the implementation of the online speech recognition system(ASR), deploying the algorithmic module to the server, and interact with the client through its own training model.

## Car file transmission system

Aug 2020 - Jan 2021

Front-end developer

This project is an innovative project, in includes manager wesite and ordinary client (Website), implemented by JSP format web, html + css + js. It has following main functions: file transferring, file path tracking, file transferring algorithm switching, and user-related business features. I mainly took responsible for the front-end development of the administrator system and developing some features of the backend.

# **HONORS & AWARDS**

## 2016.12

# **SKILLS, CERTIFICATIONS & OTHERS**

- Skills: Python, MySQL, C++, Docker, Ubuntu, FastAPI
- Languages: English (fluent CET-6)
- Interests: Football, photography, travel, learning language, programming